wealthshareclub.com 2011-11-23

# Wealth Share Club! : Privacy Policy

|    

| Privacy Policy  
---  
  
**Information Collection and Use of Information:**

In order to use Wealthshareclub, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give his contact information (email address, please use G-mail if possible). This information is used to contact the user about the service and products we provide or wish to provide. We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to others.

**Security:**

Wealthshareclub takes every precaution to protect our users personal information. When a user submits sensitive information via our site, the information is protected both online and off-line. Only the administrator of this site can access personal information of the users.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**

If a members personal information changes, we provide a way to update that members personal data provided to us. This can be done within the member area.

**Right to Cancel:**

Our users can cancel membership and be removed from all newsletters and databases. This can be done via your account. **Warning** , once deleted your account, all user information will be removed from the entire database with no recovery possible.

**Site and Service Updates:**

We may send the user, site and service announcement updates. We communicate with the users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their accounts via email.

**Notification of Changes:**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.

**Contacting Us:**

Please use our Contact to communicate with us.
